Did you know?
The US and Houthi forces in Yemen have agreed to a temporary ceasefire.
But, here’s the catch.
The Houthis say they’ll evaluate the proposal before making a final decision.
President Trump announced this move after the Houthis promised to halt their attacks on American ships.
This is significant because it could lead to peace talks between the Yemeni government and the Houthis, potentially ending years of conflict in the war-torn nation.
So, what does this mean?
It’s a step towards de-escalation, but we’ll have to wait and see if both parties hold their end of the deal.
Remember to like, share and subscribe for more updates on Global News.
Stay informed, stay engaged.