In today's news, we're looking at a significant development in Sudan.
Did you know that for the first time ever, Port Sudan, the wartime capital of the country, has been hit by drone attacks?
This attack on an army-held city signals a worrying escalation in the two-year-long civil war.
The conflict between the Sudanese military and a powerful paramilitary group, the Rapid Support Forces, has been ongoing since October 2021.
The use of drone attacks marks a new level of intensity in this already devastating conflict.
So why does this matter?
Well, these drone attacks pose a serious threat to civilian safety and could potentially destabilize the region even further.
It's crucial to stay informed about such developments as they unfold.
Remember to like, share, and subscribe for more updates on global news events.
Stay tuned as we continue to bring you insights into the world around us.