Title.
Benjamin Netanyahu's moves right now could change everything.
Narration.
Hello.
Today we dive into the political landscape of Israel, focusing on its long-serving prime minister, Benjamin Netanyahu.
Despite facing corruption charges, his recent moves could reshape the Middle East.
Netanyahu has formed a unity government with his rival, Benny Gantz, ending over a year of political deadlock.
This alliance, while temporary, aims to manage Israel's challenges amidst regional tensions and the COVID-19 pandemic.
But wait, there's more!
Netanyahu's cabinet includes several hardliners who might take Israel in new directions, such as annexing West Bank territories.
This move could change the balance of power in the Middle East and impact peace negotiations with Palestine.