Title Why California's Rush for Real ID in 2025 Opening shot Close up of a passport and driver's license side by side Narration Ever wondered what's the difference between your passport and driver's license?
It's all about security, especially in California.
As we approach 2025, the Golden State is gearing up to roll out the Real ID.
Cut to a montage of people at the DMV.
Narration.
But why the rush?
After the 9-11 attacks, the US government passed the Real ID Act.
It aims to set federal standards for driver's licenses and ID cards, making them secure enough for domestic flights.
Cut to an image of a plane taking off.
narration without real id your license won't cut it at airports come 2025 so if you're planning a trip remember this real id by 2025 closing shot logo of the channel narration stay tuned for more updates on real id and other essential info like share and subscribe